Tigran Khachatryan

tigran.khachatryan	.2022@gmail.com	
	+374 77 87 17 79	

Apt. Mikoyan 14/12, Yerevan, Armenia

08 September, 2000

www.linkedin.com/in/khachatryantigran in

github.com/TigranKhachatryan2000 (

I am a Front-end developer with 3 years of experience who is currently looking for opportunities to implement new projects and attain new skills. I gained huge developing skills and proficiency in different programming frameworks during my academic and career. I'd especially underline my abilities in working with JavaScript programming language as I have always been in interaction with projects containing those frameworks. My services are fast and reliable. You can contact me any time. Thank you for your interest.

EDUCATION

Bachelor

National Polytechnic University of Armenia

09/2018 - 06/2024 Armenia/Yerevan Courses

Information Systems

Master's degree

National Polytechnic University of Armenia

09/2024 - Present Armenia/Yerevan Courses

Systems with artificial intelligence

Introduction to React and **Node.js Armenian Code Academy**

09/2021 - 03/2022

Armenia/Yerevan

- Courses - Started learning Programing basics
- Create a Web application using React and Redux

- Learned how to work with team.

SKILLS

React, Next.js	• • • • •
JavaScript,TypeScript	••••
Node.js/Express.js	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ
Redux/Retux Toolkit	
HTML/CSS/SASS/Bootstrap	• • • • 0
GIT/GitLab/Azure	• • • • •
C++/OOP	
SQL/Mongo DB	

LANGUAGES

Russian **English** Professional Working Basic Working **Proficiency Proficiency**

INTERESTS

Books Music Films Chess Sports

WORK EXPERIENCE

React Developer

Rocket Systems

03/2022 - 05/2022

Web and Mobile Development

Soft Construct

06/2022 - Present Web and Mobile Development Armenia/Yerevan

Armenia/Yerevan